Hey everyone, welcome to another video. It's a jumpsuit up video and I'm going to show you
this catsuit
I'm going to try it on and
tell you a bit about it because it's like the first red PVC catsuit I'm showing you and
I'm pretty excited about it because it has some cool design features and yeah, I'm going to
Show it to you in a sec
But first I have to say thank you to Greg who gifted me this catsuit because he was like
you have to try this it's so cool and good-fitting and I agree so thanks a lot Greg.
The specialties here are quite a few for one the bust cups here which are
shaped according to the female body size and then we have a special cut here at
the back side and bottom which enhances the shape of the booty a bit. Another
feature is the zipper. There are two zippers one in the back and one in the
crotch which makes the catsuit even more comfortable because then you don't have
one really long zipper and the fabric can stretch here in between so it's
comfortable for wearing. And at the hemlines here you have like double
double edged seams which is also something I quite rarely see at PVC
catsuits. The fabric is a red four-way stretch PVC, really smooth and stretchy.
Yeah so this is really really cool catsuit, cool design and you'll see in a
how it's going to look when I'm wearing it.
It's tight but the material is super stretchy so it's definitely working, fitting good.
To really emphasize the cup I'm going to wear it without a bra today.
would be better fitting to a red catsuit than red boots. You may have seen them in the boot
video for this one. I'll link it here everywhere, whatever. And yeah, I'm going to wear them
now and see how they look together.
That looks so cool together with the red boots.
I'm like in love with this outfit combination.
I mean it's not the exact same red color with the two of them but it's working out pretty
well so I really like this I mean look at how the catsuit fits I really have to
say it is comfy it is comfy I can move it's stretchy I thought that the arms
would be too short but they stretch as well and it fits so good like figure
hugging whatever. That's so cool. So Greg you're right this catsuit cut with all the
specialties here really is something else apart from your normal plain PVC
catsuit. I just realized that the material is slightly see-through so
really only slightly so you kind of have to wear it without underwear although I
I mean if you're wearing it for a party and whatever and you want to go to the toilet with a crotch zipper
because everyone is always asking how do you go to the toilet?
There's a crotch zipper so you shouldn't wear underwear.
Anyway, the company by the way is called Winter Fetish.
Although in the catsuit the label says Tasty Tiger which is pretty funny name but I have no idea what's the relation there.
Anyway, winter fetish, I ordered it there, everything went well.
Really good thing again is that there is a long version of the skat seat.
I'm not having any problems with the length here because it's, like I said, a long version,
which makes it even more comfortable and makes me like it even better. I don't know, yeah.
I added a belt for the very extra touch. I don't know if it's too much or still okay.
What do you think? Leave a comment down below the video. Yeah, I mean this is definitely an outfit
I would wear to a party. Like a fetish party. But it's super comfortable and looks so cool.
still not over how this looks so cool
I think I'm going to take some pictures with it for sure
now after this video so follow me on Instagram or whatever if you want to see them
all right that was it again I hope you had fun with this video I hope you like this catsuit
as much as I do because I do thanks again to Greg yeah I don't know what
else to say have a splendid day this year around bye